Thrive with Adult ADHD

[Home](https://adhdboss.com/) » Privacy Policy

Ezoic Services
==============

Ezoic Services  
This website uses the services of Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), including to manage third-party interest-based advertising. Ezoic may employ a variety of technologies on this website, including tools to serve content, display advertisements and enable advertising to visitors of this website, which may utilize first and third-party cookies.  
A cookie is a small text file sent to your device by a web server that enables the website to remember information about your browsing activity. First-party cookies are created by the site you are visiting, while third-party cookies are set by domains other than the one you're visiting. Ezoic and our partners may place third-party cookies, tags, beacons, pixels, and similar technologies to monitor interactions with advertisements and optimize ad targeting. Please note that disabling cookies may limit access to certain content and features on the website, and rejecting cookies does not eliminate advertisements but will result in non-personalized advertising. You can find more information about cookies and how to manage them [here](https://allaboutcookies.org/).  
The following information may be collected, used, and stored in a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP address
* Operating system type and version
* Device type
* Language preferences
* Web browser type
* Email (in a hashed or encrypted form)

Ezoic and its partners may use this data in combination with information that has been independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements across various platforms and websites. Ezoic’s partners may also gather additional data, such as unique IDs, advertising IDs, geolocation data, usage data, device information, traffic data, referral sources, and interactions between users and websites or advertisements, to create audience segments for targeted advertising across different devices, browsers, and apps. You can find more information about interest-based advertising and how to manage them [here](https://youradchoices.com/).  
You can view Ezoic’s privacy policy [here](https://ezoic.com/privacy/), or for additional information about Ezoic’s advertising and other partners, you can view Ezoic’s advertising partners [here.](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/)

============================================================================

[**Last updated:** December 22nd, 2019

ADHD Boss respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use ADHD Boss’s services (“ADHD Boss Services”). Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission or as explained in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

**ADHD Boss and Cookies**
-------------------------

Upon your first visit to ADHDBoss.com, ADHD Boss sends a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. ADHD Boss uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. ADHD Boss does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people use the ADHD Boss Services. ADHD Boss will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the ADHD Boss Services may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

**Third Party Cookies**
-----------------------

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Policy against advertising our website using unsolicited email messages**
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

We require that all e-mails promoting ADHDBoss.com or its products are sent only to clients who have agreed to receive such messages. We prohibit any advertising of our brand and website using unsolicited email messages. Not complying with this policy will cause partnership termination and/or affiliate account termination.

If you feel you’ve been sent unsolicited emails promoting our brand or website and would like to register a complaint, please email us (stef@ADHDBoss.com). We will immediately investigate all allegations made related to unsolicited messages.

**What Information Do We Collect?**
-----------------------------------

ADHD Boss does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. For example, ADHD Boss DOES collect such information from those users registering as Community Users and/or User Editors. ADHD Boss notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. For example, ADHD Boss may use your IP address or browser language to determine which language to use when showing search results or advertisements.

**Links to Other Sites**
------------------------

The stories/sites displayed and/or linked to by the ADHDBoss.com Service are developed by people over whom ADHD Boss exercises no control. Other links are also on sites not controlled by ADHD Boss. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. ADHD Boss encourages you to read the privacy policy of all web sites you visit. ADHD Boss may choose to exhibit its results in the form of a “URL redirecter.” When ADHD Boss uses a URL redirecter, if you click on a URL on a ADHD Boss page, information about the click is sent to ADHD Boss, and ADHD Boss in turn sends you to the site you clicked on. ADHD Boss uses this URL information to understand and improve the quality of ADHD Boss’s technology.

**With Whom Does ADHD Boss Share Information?**
-----------------------------------------------

ADHD Boss may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average ADHD Boss user visits ADHD Boss, or which ADHD Boss pages are most often used. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. Further, ADHD Boss reserves the right to cooperate with legitimate law enforcement requests for information at its sole discretion.

**Children’s Privacy**
----------------------

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.  If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

**Third Party Advertising**
---------------------------](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/)

[ADHD Boss may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt out, you can visit](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/) [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). This automatically-collected data is also used by ADHD Boss to analyze trends, administer the site and track users’ use of the site.

In addition, ADHD Boss collects personally identifiable information from users (including email addresses, names, gender, date of birth, and zip code) during the registration process. This information may be used by ADHD Boss to improve our site and the overall user experience.

**Geo Location Services**
-------------------------

ADHD Boss may, through its website, iPhone applications and related sites, request your location via a geolocation service. Through this service ADHD Boss may collect, depending on the capabilities of your device, information about the wifi routers closest to you, identifying information related to the cell towers closest to you, and the strength of your wifi or cell signal. ADHD Boss will use this information to return an estimated location. This information (including your IP address) may then be used by ADHD Boss to develop new features, products or services. This information may also be shared on an aggregated or individual basis with our third party advertisers to display better-targeted advertising content.

**Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy**
--------------------------------------------------

By using the ADHD Boss Services and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. ADHD Boss may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Footer CTA
----------

### Search ADHD Boss:

Search this website

Copyright © 2021 ADHD Boss • All rights reserved • [Recommended Resources](https://adhdboss.com/resources/) • [Contact ADHD Boss](https://adhdboss.com/contact/) • [Write for ADHD Boss](https://adhdboss.com/write-for-adhd-boss/).  
  
**The information on this website has not been evaluated by the FDA, and is not intended to diagnose, treat, prevent, or cure any disease.**  
  
By accessing or using this website, you agree to abide by the [TOS](https://adhdboss.com/tos/), [Privacy Policy](https://adhdboss.com/privacy-policy/), [Medical Disclaimer](https://adhdboss.com/medical-disclaimer/), and [Affiliate Disclosure](https://adhdboss.com/affiliate-disclosure/).  

x
